module.exports = {
  gameType: 'text',
  questions: [
    {
      question: 'in the episode "go god go," the warring factions battle over the right name for their aetheist denomination. which is not one of the factions?', 
      a: 'alligned atheist order (AAO)', 
      b: 'unified atheist league (UAL)',
      c: 'united atheist alliance (UAA)',
      d: 'allied atheist allegiance (AAA)',
      answer: 'a'
    },
    {
      question: 'randy marshs marijuana farm is called', 
      a: 'brevity', 
      b: 'tegridy',
      c: 'selenity',
      d: 'tertiary',
      answer: 'b'
    },
    {
      question: 'cartmans father is', 
      a: 'dr. mephesto', 
      b: 'one of the 1989 denver boncos',
      c: 'jack tenorman',
      d: 'chef',
      answer: 'c'
    },
    {
      question: 'the music album "chef aid" did not feature a song from', 
      a: 'master p', 
      b: 'elton john',
      c: 'devo',
      d: 'phil collins',
      answer: 'd'
    },
    {
      question: 'cartmans favorite mexican restaurant is', 
      a: 'casa bonita', 
      b: 'la cortina',
      c: 'sombreros',
      d: 'three amigos',
      answer: 'a'
    },
    {
      question: 'what is the name of matt & treys band that occassionally makes music for south park?', 
      a: 'pisswater faucets', 
      b: 'DVDA',
      c: 'bananas and blow',
      d: 'pile driver',
      answer: 'b'
    },
    {
      question: 'what is the name of the abusive boy scout leader who replaces big gay al?', 
      a: 'frank fondler', 
      b: 'small straight larry',
      c: 'mr slippyfist',
      d: 'mr mackey',
      answer: 'c'
    },
    {
      question: 'the theme song of south park is performed by', 
      a: 'mr bungle', 
      b: 'big head todd and the monsters',
      c: 'ween',
      d: 'primus',
      answer: 'd'
    },
    {
      question: 'the alter ego of butters is', 
      a: 'professor chaos', 
      b: 'general dissaray',
      c: 'the coon',
      d: 'mintberry crunch',
      answer: 'a'
    },
    {
      question: 'in a halloween episode, spooky vision refers to', 
      a: 'goggles that make ghosts appear', 
      b: 'barbara streissand\'s face in the corners of the screen',
      c: 'paris hilton under a black light',
      d: 'being hipnotized by lasers',
      answer: 'b'
    }
  ]
};